realcounter.eu 2015-05-29

# Cookies - Olihargon Advertising

The following policy describes how we collect and use personal data and it applies to all visitors of Olihargon website, including Advertisers and Publishers. By using Olihargon website, services and platform you accept this policy. At Olihargon we are committed to respect and protect the privacy of our visitors and service users. 

### What information do we collect?

Olihargon collects two types of data: Personal Data: information that you share yourself with us completing the registration form and your Olihargon profile, such as your first and last name(s), email, billing and payment information. Technical Data: geography, browser information, IP address, operating system and language. We use the most reliable technical security measures to protect your information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is entirely secure and Olihargon cannot guarantee absolute security. 

### How do we use your data?

Olihargon uses personal data to: 

  * \- Provide services: we use your personal data to provide you with our services and to identify you as well as to prevent and investigate fraud and other misuses. 
  * \- Communicate with you: we may use your personal data to communicate with you, to offer you technical/administrative assistance, to inform you if our services have changed or to send you important notifications. 

Olihargon uses technical data in order to collect statistical information, to perform anti-fraud controls and security checks in case we notice abnormal activity connected to your account, we will contact you promptly to ensure the safety of your data and credit. 

### Do we share personal data?

In general we do not sell, lease, rent or share your personal data to third parties unless otherwise stated below.

We may disclose any information we have about you (including your identity) if we determine that it is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of Olihargon website or services, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Olihargon rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to our users of the Olihargon website, including Olihargon customers. Olihargon reserves at all times, the right to disclose any information that deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Olihargon also may disclose your information when determines that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes. 

We may disclose your information in case of mergers and acquisitions.  
If we decide to sell, merge or re-organize our business, we may disclose personal data to prospective or actual buyers. 

### Changes to this policy

Olihargon may occasionally update this policy in order to reflect changes in our services. In case of changes the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this page will be updated and we will send a notification to our users (both Advertisers and Publishers). If you are a visitor, we recommend that you re-visit this policy from time to time to learn of any changes. 

Cookies are pieces of information that a website places on your device when you visit a website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use cookies to bring together information we collect about you. You can choose to have your device warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. 

You do this through your browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. Please see the last section of this Cookies Policy for more information about how to manage or disable browser cookies. 

We use cookies to securely store your login information to allow you to login without writing each time the userID and password, for security purposes and for customizing your visits and referral tracking.  
If you don`t agree, you can delete temporarly, or disable cookies entirely in your browser or only for this website as explained in the answer below.

There are a number of ways for you to manage cookies and other tracking technologies.  
Through your browser settings, you can accept or decline cookies or set your browser to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.   
You should be aware that you may not be able to use all our features if you set your browser to disable cookies entirely. 

If you are not using any of the above-listed common browsers, you could find the relative settings in the browser menu or settings. 

Last Update: May 22 2015
